(Howard:)...but you wouldn't have to
because there are no women in them.
(Raj:)Gotcha.
(Raj:)I'll have a Brandy Alexander.
(Howard:)All right, the Three Musketeers
just became the Dynamic Duo.
- Should we talk to some of these women?
- No, it's way too early in the night for that.
(Howard:)See, first we let the lawyers
and the jocks thin the herd...
(Howard:)...and then we go after the weak
and the old and the lame.
- That's your system?
- That's my system.
(Howard:)Oh, and if you spot a chick
with a Seeing Eye dog, she's mine.
(Howard:)Oh, come on.
(Penny:)I think it's nice that Captain Sweatpants
showed up to your art opening.
Yeah. It would've been nicer
if he hadn't touched all the cheese.
(Penny:)Um, you know, it's kind of early.
Wanna maybe come in for coffee
or something?
(Stuart:)Oh, gee, it's a little late for coffee,
isn't it?
Oh, you think "coffee" means coffee.
That is so sweet.